One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Oars' Awakening and
Brook vs. Ryuma!
Let's get started!
W-What's this...?
A-A giant's corpse...?
Even for a giant it's too big!
Don't make a sound, Chopper.
Calm down, Straw Hat Luffy's Shadow.
I'm your new master.
You'll receive a new voice and body to live as a zombie from now on.
Forget every connection with your previous human body.
Submit to me and become my loyal soldier.
We have a deal then.
Cindry-chan, you also entered a contract to forget your past existence...
So we should be able to eat with plates.
It would be best if your knees were broken as well.
Scary!
Cindry-chan, that threat was way too scary!
Cindry is really strict with Hogback.
Now, awake...!
T-The shadow...!
From your 500 year slumber!
Luffy's shadow was...
It's in.
No! Don't yell!
The corpse moved!
What?
D-Damn it! We've been found!
We screamed!
The demon has awakened!
Hey, Kumashi!
Don't tell me you've been hiding those pirates!
My bride!
Why's she here?!
Splendid!
What violence!
It's a masterpiece!
Truly a devil!
Meat!
I'm hungry!
Hey! Where did the pirates...? Where did my bride go?!
They ran at full speed!
They sure are fast!
You won't escape!
Sanji, food!
Who's this Sanji?
What happened...?
What happened just now?
It started moving as soon as Luffy's shadow was inserted!
So that's how zombies work!
That was what Dr. Hogback meant by "giving back life!"
That huge man's ability...
It's probably a devil fruit ability!
The fact his first word was "meat" means...
That giant monster without a doubt holds Luffy's personality.
Ah, right.
Then, if I remember correctly...
That Sanji-like penguin we met at the bridge...
Even if I die...
I won't hurt a lady!
I see!
Then, Sanji's shadow was embedded into it.
Most likely.
So, the samurai who hit us with the back of the sword...
That's Brook!
Incredible!
So all those strange incidents were tied together.
These terrible zombies are just a game to him!
He's just toying with people's lives!
What "mankind dream"...!
What "bringing back the dead"...!
Dr. Hogback is a great man!
I highly respect him!
He doesn't want to help anyone in the least!
He's just another villain!
Chopper...
This isn't the time to be crying over that.
Our friends are becoming victims of this zombie game!
Do you understand?
We have to save them!
Hurry up!
We're going to where Luffy's being transported!
Yea, they said to "take them back to the ship"!
I wonder if they meant the Sunny?
If the same thing happened to Zoro and Sanji...
They must be there as well!
You're right!
Let's go help 'em!
Usopp!
Chopper!
Are you okay?!
What?
It hurts, what're you-?!
Let go of me!
This guy...!
What strength!
Are you done saying goodbye?
Today I'll marry this woman.
Idiot...
For the manly Usopp, there's no point in living...
If he can't protect even one woman!
Usopp, that weapon...!
Take this!
Six Chambered Viper Star!
He's disappearing again!
What? Even me?
Nami disappeared too!
Nami!
Where are you?!
What?
Her scent is being erased by another smell!
Help me!
Usopp, Cho-!
Hey! Nami, what's wrong?!
Where are you?!
Answer me, Nami!
Zombies!
I'll leave them to you.
Take those two to Moria-sama!
Huh?
Where's he talking from?!
What?! An armored zombie?!
More zombies are coming from below!
Zombies are coming from above too!
Hey, pirates...!
Hand over your shadows!
Don't get caught, they'll steal our shadows!
Y-Yea.
There's also portrait zombies!
Damn!
It's unfair to make an undead dog-pile!
Unfair!
We're just gonna take your shadow, bro.
Damn, let me go!
Damn!
Hey, someone's there!
They're purifying the others!
Get your dirty hands off...
My little brothers!
Who're these guys?!
They're extremely dangerous!
B...!
Big Bro!
Robin!
Didn't we make it on time?
There's one missing.
Usopp.
Chopper.
Are you hurt?
Impossible!
Aside from the Humming One, other bastards who know our weak point have appeared!
This is terrible!
"We can't die" was our catchphrase, I don't wanna spend my days in fear of annihilation!
I heard that those whose shadows were taken are carried past these long stairs.
That's right, Luffy was transported through here!
We were going after him, but then Nami...!
I wonder if Nami's okay...
It wasn't like he wanted to exterminate her. We'll definitely be back to rescue her!
By the way...
That monster-like growl coming from upstairs...
What was it?
Yeah, we went there after we heard it.
That was Luffy's voice...
We'll tell you everything we witnessed.
Anyway... something terrible has happened!
Keep delivering more!
He hasn't had enough yet!
How much can the Special Zombie eat?!
He's gonna eat the whole island's provisions!
What an amazing appetite.
Kumashi, why were you hiding those pirates?!
But... that's...
Stop talking, it's un-cute!
Sorry, tiny leek.
I don't know you and yet you're feeding me.
Even though it tastes terrible and isn't enough.
Damn you Special Zombie!
Don't act so cheeky!
Who do you think makes us, zombies, move?!
How can you even complain to the ruler of Thriller Bark?!
The Master will someday become ruler of this sea-
We're really sorry!
This guy said all that!
You, don't sell out your friends!
Listen, Oars.
500 years ago you were a huge villain who left numerous legends behind.
And now you've been resurrected to become my servant in this present day.
Servant?
I don't want that.
I have a dream.
I've never seen such an insolent zombie!
It's cramped and boring here.
I'm gonna go outside for a bit.
Maybe go out to sea and go around the world.
Going on a trip?!
You blockhead, that's impossible.
This special freezer is made from super dense steel and it's completely sealed.
You won't be able to scratch it in the leas-
Rubber...
Pistol!
H-Hey! Wait!
This is terrible, Oars has escaped!
Strange...
I had a feeling that my arm would stretch but... well, whatever.
I'm gonna be... the Pirate King!
Just like then...
Pleading "not the afro", "not the afro"... You'll wind up shamelessly begging me for your life again.
No!
It won't go that way!
It's pointless.
Even if I muster my courage and cut them, those scary zombies keep getting up!
They definitely must have a weakness.
At this rate, even if I find my own zombie, there wouldn't be anything I could do.
More than anything, zombies' faces are just too scary!
One of ours was purified!
What happened?!
He was hungry and ate some salty grilled fish.
Idiot, he was a newcomer.
This must be the zombies' weakness!
You! You're the skeleton whose shadow we stole a few days ago.
How did you get back here?
Answer my question!
Which zombie has my shadow?
If you don't answer, I'll scatter fish all over the island!
Fish...?
And how's that gonna affect me?
That's...
No way...
But, I don't think it could be salt...
Salt...?
A-And h-how is salt g-gonna do any good?!
It's salt!
Zombies are really, really scary after all.
It's even worse during the night.
What, it was just a grasshopper.
It scared me.
Nonetheless, it's even more dangerous when the sun is shining, and it's easy to be found by the enemy.
That's it!
Sing!
When you're scared you should sing a song to take your mind off things!
I'll be able to purify them if I don't look at their faces by using my skeleton speed.
Then, I'll definitely find my shadow!
What's this song?
Someone's humming.
Who is it?!
What's wrong?!
What's all the ruckus on the island about?!
There's a warrior with a scary face who appears when you hear humming in the darkness!
He's going around trying to find his shadow!
He already annihilated most of the Soldier Zombies!
Please do something!
Perona-sama, there's trouble...
Shut up!
Don't wake me, Kumashi...
Please wake up...
We finally meet.
What's with this strength?
Isn't this my zombie...?
I can't keep up with him at all!
Even though we share the same sword style!
Give up.
Regardless of how many times you try, it'll be the same.
If you try to move quicker, I'll cut off that ridiculous afro of yours.
P-Please don't!
Please don't touch the afro!
Please!
Why don't you know?!
If you're my shadow, then why don't you know how important this afro is?
Since my body no longer ages, it'll never grow again!
Why, you ask?
I've forgotten everything about my days with you.
Right now, I only obey Moriah-sama and Absalom-sama!
A skeleton who treasures his afro is nothing but a joke to me!
Stop!
Not the afro!
What a miserable look, my former master.
I'm sorry... I've lost...
Please let me off...
I'll leave this island immediately.
Then, get out of my sight.
It'll be troublesome for me if you die.
It was a pathetic sight.
Say anything you want.
These past five years...
Just for this moment...!
I became stronger!
Absalom-sama.
Is everything ready for the ceremony?
Anytime you want.
What a beautiful bride!
We'll start the ceremony immediately.
Put her in a dress and bring her to the ceremonial hall.
Yes, right away.
A monster bigger than giants?!
Yes...
That incredible noise and roar were his doing.
I can only imagine that's Luffy's zombie roaring and rampaging.
Let's hurry!
Hey, look!
There's the Sunny!
I see...
If you head straight up you'll find the boss's room.
Are those stairs used for unloading?
Hey!
The whole place has been messed up!
No doubt it's the zombies' doing.
It's full of muddy footprints.
Then, they might still be there...
A complete mess indeed.
There's barely anything left.
Is there any zombie around...?
First of all, where could they be...?
I don't see them.
Hey!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Hey, they're in the dining room!
The three of them!
The zombies completely re-decorated them.
Pitiful.
Wake up!
This isn't time the for a nap!
We have serious problems!
They're still asleep.
Did they feel anything at all?
It can't be helped.
Hey, step back, I'm gonna use the bazooka.
No, it's fine.
A beautiful female swordmaster has brought a lot of meat!
Beautiful?
Meat?
Swordmaster?
They're hopeless!
Translation & initial syncing, Vegapunk Fansubs
Syncing, Galaxy 9000, , Sync-checking, Sewil
Quality checking, Sewil
Video editing, Sewil
Soundtracking, Halee